slco.org 2012-11-07

# - Privacy Statement - Salt Lake County

### General

This web site is maintained and operated by Salt Lake County, Utah. For questions or comments regarding this site contact [webadmin@slco.org](http://www.slco.org/tools/mail/mail.cfm?PID=150&OID=14100&CC=0).

Salt Lake County (SLCo) respects the privacy of every individual who visits our web sites. This Privacy Statement outlines the information Salt Lake County will collect and how Salt Lake County will use that information. 

### Personally Identifiable Information

When you visit SLCo web sites we will not collect any personally identifiable information about you (such as your name, address, telephone number, social security number, or e-mail address) unless you provide it to us voluntarily. 

SLCo may request personally identifiable information from you in order to provide the requested service. Once collected the information is stored electronically indefinitely.

**Should you wish not to provide any Personally Identifiable Information you may utilize the services by using the appropriate non electronic means**.

The information collected may include, but is not limited:

  * First and Last names 
  * Physical address 
  * Email address 
  * Telephone number 
  * Bank account information 
  * Social Security Number 
  * Parcel Number 
  * Birth Date 
  * Origin of Birth

### Use of Personally Identifiable Information

**All of these matters and other information may be lawfully classified as Private or Controlled in accordance with the Government Records Access and Management Act (GRAMA).** SLCo may store and process your personally identifiable information to better understand your needs and how we may improve our electronic services and we may use your personally identifiable information to contact you if so requested by you (for example, we may send you a questionnaire or we may respond to your comments or requests for information). 

SLCo will not give your personally identifiable information to any outside organization unless required by law. 

### Non Personally Identifiable Information

SLCo may collect information about you that is not personally identifiable. Examples of this type of information include IP address, time of visit, the type of internet browser or computer operating system you are using, and the domain name of the web site from which you linked to our sites. SLCo uses this information to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our web site. We also use it to gather broad demographic information about our users in general. This information does not contain anything that can identify users personally. 

Additionally SLCo may store some information on your computer. This information will be in the form of a "cookie". Most internet browsers enable you to erase cookies from your computer hard drive, block all cookies, or receive a warning before a cookie is stored. Please refer to your browser instructions or help screen to learn more about these functions. 

SLCo will not attempt to tie any personally identifiable information on individual users to non personally identifiable information. 

### Security

SLCo is committed to keeping secure the data you provide us and will take reasonable precautions to protect your personally identifiable information from loss, misuse, or alteration. SLCo employs industry standards in securing this information. 

### Non SLCo Web Sites

SLCo links to various non SLCo web sites. SLCo is not responsible for the content or the privacy policies of web sites to which it may provide links. 

SLCo recommends that visitors to non County sites check the privacy statements of these sites and be cautious about providing personally identifiable information without a clear understanding of how the information will be used.

Visitors may also wish to consult privacy guidelines such as those recommended by the Online Privacy Alliance. 

### Contacting Us Regarding   
Your Personally Identifiable Information

If you have submitted personally identifiable information through a SLCo web site or if someone else has submitted your personally identifiable information through a Salt Lake County web site, and you would like to have that information deleted from our databases, please contact us at [webadmin@slco.org](http://www.slco.org/tools/mail/mail.cfm?PID=150&OID=14100&CC=0 "Email Web Admin").
